http://www.hindustanlink.com/termsofuse.htm

Terms of Use
& Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
Hindustanlink.com including various internet sites / sections / sub-domains and community boards
and services, to name a few, (Hindustanlink.com Channels) hereinafter collectively
referred to as Hindustanlink.com.
Hindustanlink.com respects the privacy of it's users and is
committed to protect it in all respects.With a view to offer most enriching and
holistic internet experience to it's users Hindustanlink.com offers a vast repository of
Online Sites and variety of community services. You may read 'About Us' to know
more about Hindustanlink.com at http://www.hindustanlink.com/about_us.htm. Most of the
Online Community Services are offered for free and in some section, you may require a mandatory registration / membership to surf 'Hindustanlink.com Channels' in detail. The information
about the user as collected by Hindustanlink.com is: (a) information supplied by users and (b)
information automatically tracked while navigation
(Information).
To avail certain sites / services on our websites,
users are required to provide certain information for the registration process
namely:- a) your name, b) email address, c) sex, d) age, e) PIN code etc., and /
or your occupation, interests, and the like. (All required information is
Service Dependent). The Information as supplied by the users enables us to
improve our sites and provide you the most user-friendly experience. In some
sites as in
Contests, dating, Questions & Answers, Ask Questions / Q&A etc. we require your contact
addresses.
To improve the responsiveness of the sites for our
users, we may use "cookies", or similar electronic tools to collect information
to assign each visitor a unique, random number as a User Identification (User
ID) to understand the user's individual interests using the Identified Computer.
Unless you voluntarily identify yourself (through registration, for example), we
will have no way of knowing who you are, even if we assign a cookie to your
computer. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you
supply (an example of this is when you ask for our Personalised Horoscope). A
cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. Our advertisers may also assign
their own cookies to your browser (if you click on their ads), a process that we
do not control.
Our web servers automatically collect limited
information about your computer's connection to the Internet, including your IP
address, when you visit our site. (Your IP address is a number that lets
computers attached to the Internet know where to send you data -- such as the
web pages you view.) Your IP address does not identify you personally. We use
this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our
site to the interests of our users, to measure traffic within our site and let
advertisers know the geographic locations from where our visitors
come.
Hindustanlink.com includes links to other websites. Such sites are
governed by their respective privacy policies, which are beyond our control.
Once you leave our servers (you can tell where you are by checking the URL in
the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is
governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting.
That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of
these sites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the site
directly for more information.
When we present information to our
advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of
advertising on our website -- it is usually in the form of aggregated statistics
on traffic to various pages within our site. When you register with Hindustanlink.com, we
contact you from time to time about updation of your content to provide the
users such features that we believe may benefit you.
The Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by
entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by Hindustanlink.com or to
the people that are not engaged, employed or managed by Hindustanlink.com
We want you to
feel comfortable using our web sites
feel secure submitting information to us
contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site
know that by using our sites you are consenting to the collection of certain data
We use your email address to send you:
Password reminder and registration confirmation
Special offers
News letters
Changes in the service's policy or terms of use
Event based communications such as order information, renewal notices, invites, reminders etc.
If you use a bulletin board / forums / blogs or chat room on this site, you should be
aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can
be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could
be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for
the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these
forums.
We are the sole owners of your information collected by us at several different points on our Website.
All
information gathered on Hindustanlink.com is securely stored within the Hindustanlink.com controlled
database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to
the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective
as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot
guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information
you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the
Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the
discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet
access.
However the internet is an ever evolving medium. We may
change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future
changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be
consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless
of what the new policy may be.
Our advertisers may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser.
We use third-party advertising
companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use
information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone
number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide
advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like
more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having
this information used by these companies, click here:
Third-party advertisements may be provided by Google on our site:
# Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
# Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
# Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. (http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)
Any questions or
clarifications with respect to this Policy can be sent to Hindustanlink.com at :
jainmaonj(AT)gmail.com or by snail mail addressed to Hindustanlink.com (Privacy
Policy),
P-121, LAKE TOWN, BLOCK -B,
KOLKATA - 700 089, INDIA - or by calling our number at +91-9830068765.
BACK
Terms
of Use:
Welcome
to the Hindustanlink.com a portal for everyone.  "HINDUSTANLINK.COM".
Any references herein to hindustanlink.com shall be deemed to refer to
hindustanlink.com and/or its owners / promoters., as applicable under
the circumstances. By accessing any areas of hindustanlink.com, user(s)
agree to be legally bound and to abide by the following terms.
Copyright ©
"Hindustanlink.com"
domain registered in the year 2000. All rights reserved. All other trademarks,
images, product names, and company names and logos appearing on hindustanlink.com
are the property of their respective owners.
Trademarks
Hindustanlink.com,
custom graphics and button icons are service marks, trademarks, and/or
trade dress of hindustanlink.com, All other trademarks, product names
and company names or logos cited herein are the property of their respective
owners.
Limited
Permission to Copy
Hindustanlink.com grants you permission to only access and make personal
use of the Site and You agree not to, directly or indirectly download
or modify / alter / change / amend / vary / transform / revise / translate
/ copy / publish / distribute or otherwise disseminate any content on
Hindustanlink.com’s Site / Service, or any portion of it; or delete
or fail to display any promotional taglines included in the Site / Service
either directly or indirectly, except with the express consent of Hindustanlink.com.
However, you may print or download extracts from these pages for your
personal / individual, non-commercial use only. You must not retain any
copies of these pages saved to disk or to any other storage medium except
for the purposes of using the same for subsequent viewing purposes or
to print extracts for personal / individual use.
Hindustanlink.com forbids you from any attempts to resell or put to commercial
use any part of the Site; any collection and use of any product listings,
descriptions, or prices; any derivative use of the Site or its contents;
any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of any
other merchant; any renting, leasing, or otherwise transferring rights
to the Site / Service; displaying the name, logo, trademark or other identifier
of another person (except for Hindustanlink.com or you) in such a manner
as to give the viewer the impression that such other person is a publisher
or distributor of the Service on the Site, or any data gathering or extraction
tools; or any use of meta tags. You may not (whether directly or through
the use of any software program) create a database in electronic or structured
manual form by regularly or systematically downloading and storing all
or any part of the pages from this site.
No part of the Site may be reproduced or transmitted to or stored in any
other web site, nor may any of its pages or part thereof be disseminated
in any electronic or non-electronic form, nor included in any public or
private electronic retrieval system or service without prior written permission.
Requests to republish Hindustanlink.com’s material for distribution
may be addressed to Hindustanlink.com, P-121, LAKE TOWN, BLOCK -B,
KOLKATA - 700 089, INDIA
Disclaimer
HINDUSTANLINK.COM
IS PROVIDING THIS SITE AND ITS CONTENTS ON AN "AS IS" BASIS AND
MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WITH RESPECT TO THIS
SITE OR ITS CONTENTS. HINDUSTANLINK.COM DISCLAIMS ALL SUCH REPRESENTATIONS
AND WARRANTIES, INCLUDING FOR EXAMPLE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN ADDITION, HINDUTANLINK.COM DOES NOT
REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE CONTENT/ INFORMATION ACCESSIBLE VIA THIS SITE
IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT. Price and availability information
or any other content/information is subject to change without notice.
Except as specifically stated on
this site, neither hindustanlink.com nor any of its owners, employees
or other representatives will be liable for damages / inconvenience arising
out of or in connection with the use of this site. This is a comprehensive
limitation of liability that applies to all damages of any kind, including
(without limitation) compensatory, direct, indirect or consequential damages,
loss of data, income or profit, loss of or damage to property and claims
of third parties.
AT ANY STAGE IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH
ANY PORTION OF THE HINDUSTANLINK.COM WEB SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS
OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE HINDUSTANLINK.COM
WEB SITE.
Our contact details:
http://www.hindsutanlink
email
: jainmanoj (AT) gmail.com
Hindustanlink.com,
P-121, LAKE TOWN, BLOCK -B,
KOLKATA - 700 089, INDIA - Phone +91-9830068765.
